# **Paige Godwin**

#### **Contact Information**

07850280289

Paige.Godwin@lloydsbanking.com

# **Profile Summary**

As an experienced customer service professional, I've spent 8 years immersed in understanding customer needs and finding a way to meet these. I've witnessed first-hand where processes or systems have let both the customer and colleague down. Driven by my desire to seek out where I can make a meaningful impact on improving and enhancing the customer experience, I recently embarked on a reskill journey as a software engineer. As I continue to develop end embed these skills, I'm seeking an opportunity to contribute to a team focussed on delivering customer focussed solutions.

#### **Tech Stack**

- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- Java
- Spring
- Databases with MySQL
- Testing with Selenium
- GitHub

## Key skills

- Communication
- Collaboration
- · Leadership
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability

# **Experience**

#### Full Stack Software Engineer Reskill (Secondment)

#### November 2023-Present

- Completed 12 weeks reskill training in full stack development, supplementing my learning with further independent research
- Collaborated in groups and pairs, to deliver several projects, focussing on frond end, back end and testing
- Adopted an agile scrum methodology actively taking part and leading sprint planning, daily stand up's, sprint reviews and retrospectives
- Utilised a variety of internal and external resources to problem solve and build more complex applications

### Team Manager – Fraud and Disputes

#### February 2023-November 2023

- After my previous secondment ended due to a restructure I utilised the opportunity to gain new skills, opting to train in Fraud, taking on additional responsibility of approving high value cases of up to £10,000
- Adapted quickly to the new skills and supported a new team to competency remotely, keeping colleagues engaged by running "Fun Friday's"

#### Business Analyst - Homeworking Controls (Secondment)

#### October 2021-February 2023

 Independently managed approx. 60 new cases a month of criminal and financial vetting for all prospective homeworkers in consumer relationships, managing my time effectively to conduct interviews and process the data to complete cases within SLA

- Identified issues with colleague understanding of the vetting process and reshaped all communications, reducing colleague queries entirely
- Identified a population of colleagues who did not have valid vetting in place and were in breach of the agreed risk controls, informing senior stakeholders and creating and leading a project to ensure compliance, implementing further guidelines to reduce breaches
- Proactively shadowed other colleagues within the team and progressed to support with the wider activities of onboarding new homeworkers
- Built a network of relationships with stakeholders across office locations to facilitate continuous communication on progress and enable outstanding actions to be chased
- Confidently presented a business case to senior stakeholders to increase FTE in the team
- Gathered evidence and data to support a second business case to remove the outdated vetting requirements, resulting in a reduction in onboarding time from 6 weeks to 2 weeks
- Managing additional projects resulting in 100% increase in workload, collaborating closely within our small team to ensure all deadlines were met

#### Team Manager - Banking

#### December 2018-November 2023

- Lead several new teams to competency, building a team culture to drive performance and reduce absence
- Coached and mentored aspiring team managers to build the required skills to progress into the role
- Embraced and delivered change, influenced colleagues to ensure change landed positively and was embedded
- Monitored colleague performance and used available information to identify areas for development. Worked with colleagues to set achievable goals, regularly reviewed and adapted to changes in performance
- Took ownership of my own development and set time aside to complete any actions

#### Banking Customer Advisor

## December 2015 - December 2018

- Communicated effectively with customers to establish their needs and find effective solutions to meet those needs
- Volunteered and was successful in becoming a "Best Bank Connector" and moderated colleague communications and to ensure the successful delivery of changes
- Became an SME in both banking and online banking, collaborating with credit card skilled colleagues within the team to improve the customer experience and reduce hand off's to separate teams

#### Tesco Customer Advisor

April 2013-December 2015

#### Education

- Level 3 Apprenticeship Cardiff and Vale College December 2019
  Senior Customer Advisor In Financial Services
- BBB at A Level Ysgol Gyfun Gwynllyw August 2013 Chemistry, Physics, Mathematics